Guide to the Yale Daily News Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographic negatives used in the publication of the Yale Daily News, 1957-1982; Series I
  - 1975
    - 1975 February 1-27
      - Purim Serulees at Hillel, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Davenport Chamber music Concert, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Hamburger, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Hunger speech, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Women employees in dining hall, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - PU debate on Woodward report, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Model UN, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Minority women's conference, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Kids on Playground, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Hayfever season, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Ghost Sonata, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - 1975 March 1 - April 23
      - Hockey v. Harvard, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Eastern Wrestling, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Volleyball Finals, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Lacrosse atWesleyan, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Basketball v. U Conn, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Baseball v. S. Conn, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Baseball v. Wesleyan, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Lacrosse v. Princeton, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Track v. Harvard, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Women's Squash v. Harvard, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Crew v. Coast Guard, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Baseball v. Quinnipiac, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Track Practice, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Baseball v. Princeton, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - AYA Meeting, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Yale Composers, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Tennis v. Trinity, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - UN Panel Discussion, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Beer can bottom in root of HGS spire, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Jimmy Carter TD Chubb Fellow, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - ID photos, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Figure skating, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - CIA Conference, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Music of the High Italian Renaissance, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - TD dining hall dish washer, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Food day fair, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - 1975 May 6 - August 8
      - Summer Term, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - Speaker's Stand (Old Campus), 1975 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - Neuter Rooster/Malt by Lakes, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - Swimming, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - Enlightenment Meeting, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - Rowing Champs, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - Refrigerator, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - Silliman Annex-English paper, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - Shuttle bus/band lecture Nursing Home, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - New Haven under the (British) Crown, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - September 5-28, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Lacrosse Practice, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Women's Field Hockey Practice, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Football v. U Conn, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Yale shuttle bus/new AYA HQ, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Voter registration at NH Hall of Records, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Branford Courtyard Joke, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - New Haven Dem. Mayoral Primary, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Logue election headquarters, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Yale dorm bathroom booze bottles, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Course books at Co-op, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Movie ticket buyers, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Dwight Hall Jamboree, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Yale Band at CCL, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - People buying film society tickets, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Rain (standing alone), 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Coors beer cans, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - 1975 October 2-30
      - Soccer Practice, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Football v. Colgate, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Field Hockey v. Dartmouth, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Rugby v. Colgate, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Football v. Brown, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Cross Country v. Columbia and Dartmouth, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Soccer v. Brown, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Miscellaneous Football, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Football v. Columbia, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Soccer v. Columbia, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Soccer v. S Conn, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Mock Trial, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Soccer v. Springfield, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Rugby v. Cornell, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Freshman Football v. Milford Academy, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Football v. Cornell, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Soccer v. Cornell, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Field Hockey v. Cornell, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Crew-Head of the Charles Regatta, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - JE Jamboree, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Aviation/Art Project Stand, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Women's Ice Hockey, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Men's Ice Hockey, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Alumni reunion classes of 35and36, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - IBM Panel, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Biology lab in progress, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Crime-CCL, ID checking, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Bartending-mixing drinks and drinking, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Genetics talk (Biology Seminar), 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Wood pile shots, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Class ring display at Co-op, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Law School alumni, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Class ring shots (hand of Jefferson), 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Welfare dept., 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Rainy day shots, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Crowded CCL, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Med school exhibit, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Union Workers and washing machine under milkweed, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Proof of the Pudding, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Singing concert-Peirson Common room, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Black students at Yale-President and other, 1975 October (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - 1975 November 1-25
      - Football v. Dartmouth, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Rugby v. Dartmouth, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Cross Country v. Harvard Princeton, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Bladderball, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Football v. Penn, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Soccer v. Farmington, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Basketball Practice, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Field Hockey v. S. Conn, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Football v. Princeton, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Soccer v. Princeton, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Field Hockey v. Princeton, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Soccer v. Harvard, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Football v. Harvard, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Field Hockey v. Harvard, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Acoustical String Concert, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Sports Winter Conference, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Contest Banners, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Princeton Tiger w/ Bull Dog, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Orange St. elections/AM Foetz, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Yale Band Formation on football field, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - PDQ Bach concert, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - The man from Clairol, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - No smoking sign at CCL, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Line for Harvard tickets-Harvard Banner, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Calhoun Day-Local HS students, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Beat Harvard Signs, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Theft of Harvard Banner, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Branford Dining Hall overloading, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Pep rally for The Game, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Speech on Cypriot affairs, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Co-op election meeting, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - 1975 December 1-17
      - Basketball v. Williams, 1975 December (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Hockey v. Penn, 1975 December (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Gymnastics Practice, 1975 December (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Basketball v. Fordham, 1975 December (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Fencing Practice, 1975 December (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Hockey v. U Conn, 1975 December (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Over-worked dorm room, 1975 December (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Line at Davenport Dining Hall, 1975 December (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Shriver meeting-PU Rollin Ogtera (?) Award, 1975 December (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Phelps Gate Tour (stand alone) staff, 1975 December (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Horse back riding at armory, 1975 December (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Trial rehearsal and director person, 1975 December (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Christmas trees in Trumbull and Morse dining hall, 1975 December (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - 1976
    - 1976 January 1-31
      - Gymnastic stars, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - At Gallery, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Women's' Basketball v. Dartmouth, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Hockey v. Boston College, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Fencing v. Trinity, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Squash v. Harvard, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Fencing Practice, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Squash Practice, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Fencing Stars, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Wrestling Practice, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Wrestling v. Springfield, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Swimming v. Cornell, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Hockey v. U Mass, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Women's' Basketball v. UNH, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Basketball v. Holy Cross, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Hockey v. Olympic Team, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Hockey v. Andover, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Wrestling, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Basketball v. West Conn., 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Squash Team, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Basketball v. Columbia, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Fencing v. Columbia, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Swimming, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Basketball v. Cornell, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Wrestling v. Boston College, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - 1976 February 2-28
      - Standing alone, Spring at CCL, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Swimming v. Harvard, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Hockey v. Princeton, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Women's Swimming v. S Conn, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Squash v. Trinity, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Freshman Crew, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - JV Hockey, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Track v. Dartmouth, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Polo v. Cornell, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Volleyball v. New Palth, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Squash v. Cornell, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Swimming v. Springfield, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Wrestling v. Princeton, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Basketball v. Penn, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Wrestling v. Penn, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Hockey v. BU, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Men's Gymnastics, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Women's Gymnastics, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Women's Basketball vs. Radcliffe, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Men's Swimming Practice, 1976 February (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - 1976 March 11 - April 17
      - The bionic women, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Howie the Styrofoam cup, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Sports trainers, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Crew v. BU, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Track v. Army and Columbia, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - NCAA National Wrestling, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Women's; Lacrosse v. Brown, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Tennis v. Columbia, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Crew Practice, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Crew v. Coast Guard, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Baseball v. Columbia and Penn, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Tennis v. Dartmouth, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - 1976 September 13-29
      - Soccer v. U of Hartford, 1976 September (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - Soccer v. Brown, 1976 September (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - Kentwell-Oxfield Hockey Coach, 1976 September (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - Field Hockey v. Brown, 1976 September (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - Football v. Brown, 1976 September (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - Cross Country v. U Conn, 1976 September (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - Football v. V. U conn, 1976 September (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - Soccer v. U Conn, 1976 September (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - Field Hockey v. U Conn, 1976 September (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - Soccer v. Tel Aviv, 1976 September (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - 1976 October 2-31
      - Field Hockey v. Williams, 1976 October (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Field Hockey v. Barnard, 1976 October (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Water Polo v. U Conn, 1976 October (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Cross Country v. Quinnipiac, 1976 October (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Soccer v. Columbia, 1976 October (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Soccer v. Radcliffe, 1976 October (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Soccer v. Army, 1976 October (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Women's Soccer Tournament, 1976 October (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Soccer v. Cornell, 1976 October (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Football v. Lehigh, 1976 October (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Football v. Dartmouth, 1976 October (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Football v. Columbia, 1976 October (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Football v. Penn, 1976 October (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Football v. Cornell, 1976 October (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Women's Field Hockey, 1976 October (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - 1976 November 5-27
      - Field Hockey Coach and Captain, 1976 November (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - Bladderball, 1976 November (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - Soccer v. Princeton, 1976 November (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - Harvard Game Fans and Stands, 1976 November (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - Soccer v. Harvard, 1976 November (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - Basketball v. Arcadia, 1976 November (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - Football v. Princeton, 1976 November (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - Football v. Harvard, 1976 November (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - Soccer v. Harvard, 1976 November (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - Field Hockey v. Harvard, 1976 November (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - Cozza's Farewell, 1976 November (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - Hockey v. N. Eastern, 1976 November (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - 1976 December 1-9
      - Basketball v. Rutgers, 1976 December (Box 6, Folder 69)
      - Squash, 1976 December (Box 6, Folder 69)
      - Basketball v. Chester Academy, 1976 December (Box 6, Folder 69)
      - Women's basketball, 1976 December (Box 6, Folder 69)
      - Women's Swimming v. Brown, 1976 December (Box 6, Folder 69)
      - Men's Swimming v. Brown, 1976 December (Box 6, Folder 69)
      - Hockey v. Brown, 1976 December (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - 1977
    - 1977 January 1-31
      - 21/4 high tires, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Co-op buying books, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Art exhibit, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Misc. standing alones-The Return of the Natives, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Snow standing alones on football field, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Snow-covered Science Hall and sledding track, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Recycling truck, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Jr. lockers at St. Albans, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Snow removed after storm, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Orchestral, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Yale Cabaret, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Yale Concert Dancers, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Co-op record department, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Psychic, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - V. Hockey v. AIC, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Hockey v. RPI, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Basketball v. Williams, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Wrestling v. Springfield, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Basketball v. Dartmouth, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Gymnastics, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Basketball v. Trinity, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Squash v. Williams, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Swimming v. Princeton, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Hockey v. Cornell, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Track v. St. Johns and SCSC, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Men's Swimming v Army, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Fencing v. Rutgers, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Squash v. Dartmouth, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Basketball v. Boston College, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Basketball v. SSJC, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Trumbull Ice Rink, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Swimming v. Viscanoxa, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - JV Hockey, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Women's Ice Hockey v. Dartmouth, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Women's and Men's Squash, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Gymnastics v. MIT, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Hockey v. Dartmouth, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Howe Cup Final, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - House on Prospect near Divinity School, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Fencing v. Penn, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Squash v. Penn, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Women's Basketball v. Army, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Crew in Tank, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Sprague Hall Piano Concerto, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - 1977 February 1-28
      - YCC meeting the executive committee, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Graduate painting show in AandA, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Saybrook Acts, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Breakfast, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Parking meter, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - business form, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Guy advertising things that go bump, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Automation panel, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Calhoun Dramat (Police banner), 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - College game rooms, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Liz Manson-"The Real One", 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Track shoes, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Bach Society Concert with Linda Nichols, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Yale Cabaret Foreplay Door Play, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Wendy from the back, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Fred Price's eyes, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Thing in New Haven Hydrant /Parking Meter, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - South Africa speaker at Trumbull, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Hairdresser at Malley's, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Dartmouth winter Caratuar, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Cabaret Magazine, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Batgle and Pierson, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Women's Fencing, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Vaulting Horse, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Hockey Coaches Smith and Taylor, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Women's Swimming v. Montclair, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Basketball v. Penn, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Wrestling v. Columbia, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Women's Basketball v. Princeton, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Hockey v. UNH, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Women's Swimming v. Harvard, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Swimming v. Penn, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Hockey v. Penn, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Hockey v. Princeton, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Basketball v. Dartmouth, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Track v. Cornell, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Men's Squash, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Basketball v. Harvard, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Women's Gymnastics v. Rutgers, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Swimming v. Dartmouth, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Basketball v. Princeton, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Polo v. Cornell, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Pat Miller (women's track), 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Wrestling v. Harvard, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Basketball v. Cornell, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Basketball v. Columbia, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Wrestling v. U Mass, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Fencing v. Princeton, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Swimming v. Princeton, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Hockey Coach Taylor, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Track Coach, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Fencing v. Buchner, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Squash Racket and Ball, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Basketball v. Harvard, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - 1977 March 3 - April 26
      - Cabaret Show, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Masenati, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Kids at Winnie the Pooh Cabaret Show, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Spring time Happiness- standing alone, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Berkeley dinner for new/old masters, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Broken banister in Saybrook College, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Jugglers, bongo players at Cross Campus, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Yale Day-high school students, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Spring break-standing alones, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - NCAA ½ final- Towson vs. Sacred Heart, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - College band, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - College bowl play offs-Pierson, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Superman (play), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - The artist in perspective, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Galileo, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Kurt Weill revue-Nicholas Chapel, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Studying, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - 1978 elections, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Art Gallery- Ancient Art Exhibit, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - TD protest, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Concert chorus, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Antigone, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Champion shooting team, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Standing alone-Spring time flower sales, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Ronal Lirdtensteiner Circus on Cross Campus, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Five at Saybrook Friday Night, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Hockey v. Harvard, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Women's Basketball Tournament, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Lacrosse Practice, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Baseball Practice, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)